myvideo.co.za 2007-01-06

# MyVideo Privacy Policy

Revised: **20 November 2006**

Our privacy policy set out below is incorporated in and forms part of our terms. 

MyVideo shall take all reasonable steps to protect the personal information of users. For the purpose of this clause, "personal information" shall be defined as detailed in the Promotion of Access to Information Act 2 of 2000. This Act may be downloaded from <http://www.polity.org.za/html/govdocs/legislation/2000/act2.pdf>

### Links to other sites

We are not responsible for the privacy practices of web sites that we are linked to, or that have links to us. By clicking on a link, logo or other item, you may no longer be on our Website. To check what Internet location you are on, note the URL at the top and/or bottom of your browser. Read the posted privacy statement of any web site whenever you are interacting with it. 

###  Information we gather

#### Registration

When you register on MyVideo, we collect and store information that identifies you and your account. At this time you will be required to submit your full name, e-mail address and password. 

#### Online surveys and contests

Occasionally MyVideo conducts an online user survey to collect information about our user’s preferences. The surveys are optional and if you choose to respond, your responses will remain anonymous. Similarly we may offer contests to qualifying users in which we asked for contact and demographic information such as name, e-mail address and mailing address. None of this information is shared with third parties, except in summary form if it all. The information that we collect in the registration process and through online surveys is used to help us improve our services and to meet the needs and preferences of our users. This may include targeted advertising to you about our services. Information we gather through a contest may also be disclosed to third parties if necessary for prize fulfillment and other aspects of any contest or similar offering. 

#### Automatically gathered information

MyVideo automatically collects your browser type and browser software version in order to tailor the presentation of the services to your platform and to maintain a record of your activity on the Website. MyVideo uses cookies in order to enable users to specify unique preferences and to track user trends and patterns. Users always have the option of disabling cookies via their browser preferences. If you disable cookies on your browser however, some parts of our Website may not function as effectively or may be slower to use.   
As an automatic process, our web server software records a log file of IP addresses that access the Website. We also collect IP address information but do not ordinarily link IP addresses to your personal information. However we may use IP addresses to verify and identify a user when we think it is necessary in our discretion to enforce compliance with our terms or to protect our service, Website, users and others. 

#### E-mail to friends and referral program

MyVideo lets you invite friends to sign up, or recommend videos to others via e-mail. We also offer the ability to send friends e-mails about providing and purchasing services through MyVideo. If you use these features, we only use your friend's e-mail addresses on a onetime basis to send the requested posting and we use your e-mail address to copy you on the message or to send on your behalf.

#### Your public profile

When you register you may set up a personal profile describing your birthday, location, occupation, and other information about you. All this information is optional and not required in order to use the services at the Website.

###  How we use information 

####  Registration information

We use personal information for our own internal purposes including contacting you via e-mail to inform you about updates to our services and providing you with information relating to services at the Website. We may have to disclose your information, but only if required by law to do so. We do not rent or sell personal information to third parties under any circumstances without your express consent authorising us to do so.   
We offer a newsletter service on an opt-in basis. You may opt out of receiving our newsletters at any time.
